Guide to the Syria Collection of photographs AD.MC.036
New York University Abu Dhabi Library
- Vernacular Series (Box 4)
  - A portrait of two young men on a patio., 24 October 1970; ref576; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Damascus, Syria; Mountains/Hills; Men; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Outdoors
  - A group portrait of two men in suits, including Jareh Krikorian, and a small boy outside next to a car., Circa 1965-1975; ref577; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10 x 6.8 cm (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Boys; Children; Outdoors; Cars/Trucks; Streets/Roads; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Mountains/Hills; Transportation
  - A group portrait of seven men wearing jackets in the snow., 4 March 1970; ref578; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.3 x 7.5 cm (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Snow; Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of a man and a woman with a gun, and two small boys., Circa 1965-1975; ref579; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.3 x 7.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Arabic Writing; Syria; Women; Men; Guns; Weapons; Children; Boys; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of three men looking at a fabric sample., Circa 1965-1975; ref580; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Men; Advertisements; Photographic Prints; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Shops; Facial Hair
  - A group portrait of nine men eating near a body of water., Circa 1965-1975; ref581; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Men; Water; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Cigarettes; Radios; Hats; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Smoking; Food; Drinks/Beverages
  - Two women standing outdoors., Circa 1955-1975; ref583; Samir Color Lab, Saudi Arabia; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.8 x 6.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Women; Head Covers/Veils; Jewelry; Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Saudi Arabia; Outdoors
  - A group portrait of six men sitting on a bench., Circa 1955-1975; ref584; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.3 x 7.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Men; Outdoors; Clocks/Watches; Facial Hair; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of six young women making gestures., Circa 1955-1975; ref585; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 6 cm (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Women; Girls; Children; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A portrait of a young man in t-shirt standing outside., Circa 1955-1975; ref586; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10 x 7.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - A portrait of a woman wearing a dress standing in a garden., Circa 1955-1975; ref587; Studio Dunia, Derhagopian, Rue Fouad, 1er, Damas (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10 x 7 cm (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Women; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Arabic Writing; Syria; Outdoors; Gardens
  - A portrait of a man facing away from the camera outside., 1970; ref588; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10 x 7.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Men; Outdoors; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A group portrait of four men in or around a car., Circa 1955-1975; ref589; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Men; Cars/Trucks; Outdoors; Arabic Writing; Syria; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Transportation
  - A group portrait of four men wearing suits outdoors., Circa 1955-1975; ref590; Photo Najib, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Men; Outdoors; Syria; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Streets/Roads
  - A group portrait of several men outdoors, a few are wearing costumes., Circa 1955-1975; ref591; Triage Photo Dadour, Aleppo, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.3 x 7.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Men; Costumes; Outdoors; Photographic Prints; Aleppo, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
  - A group portrait of a woman leaning on a man, both are wearing jeans., Circa 1955-1975; ref592; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.2 x 7.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Men; Women; Arabic Writing; Syria; Streets/Roads; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of a man wearing a suit, a woman wearing a blue dress, and a young girl indoors., February 1959; ref593; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.8 x 8.8 cm (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Men; Women; Children; Girls; Houses; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Color Photography; Syria; Furnishings; Carpets/Rugs
  - A group portrait of two men and a woman sitting indoors., Circa 1955-1975; ref594; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.3 x 7.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Syria; Men; Women; Head Covers/Veils; Fezes/Tarbouches; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Furnishings; Facial Hair
  - A dog tied to a pole., Circa 1955-1975; ref595; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Dogs; Animals; Streets/Roads; Mountains/Hills; Photographic Prints; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Cars/Trucks; Transportation
  - A portrait of a man standing on top of a rock and wearing a suit., 1971; ref596; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Arabic Writing; Men; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Outdoors
  - A group portrait of three men at a table in front of a body of water (linked ref598)., Circa 1955-1975; ref597; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Hats; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Water; Men; Facial Hair; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of three men near a body of water, two are leaning on a tent and one is laying down (linked ref597)., Circa 1955-1975; ref598; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Men; Beaches; Water; Tents; Radios; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
  - A portrait of a topless man with glasses outdoors., 16 July 1975; ref599; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.4 cm (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Men; Outdoors; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Arabic Writing; Facial Hair
  - A group portrait of several young children indoors., 1970; ref600; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.3 x 7.4 cm (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Children; Boys; Girls; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Syria
  - A group portrait of two men talking at a wedding., Circa 1955-1975; ref601; Photo Cine Azad, Damascus, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 12 x 8.5 cm (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Weddings; Men; Women; Gatherings; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A portrait of a little boy with his hands on his hips., December 1955; ref602; Studio Yazouy, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.7 x 8.8 cm (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Boys; Furnishings; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Children; Toys; Christmas
  - A studio portrait of two men., 2 March 1971; ref603; Studio el Seyahe, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.5 x 8.5 cm (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Men; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Facial Hair; Facial Hair; Damascus, Syria
  - A group portrait of several men playing a sport., Circa 1955-1975; ref604; Studio Antoin, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.2 x 8.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Damascus, Syria; Men; Flags; Uniforms; Sports; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a little girl with curly hair wearing a necklace., Circa 1955-1975; ref605; Sadek Qassees, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 13 x 8.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Jewelry; Girls; Children; Arabic Writing
  - A studio portrait of two men in suits., Circa 1955-1975; ref606; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.2 x 8.4 cm (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Syria; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Facial Hair; Arabic Writing
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a uniform and a cap., 3 February 1974; ref607; Studio Alsabah, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.3 x 9 cm (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Damascus, Syria; Men; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Hats; Facial Hair; Medals/Insignia
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a uniform and a cap., Circa 1955-1975; ref608; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.4 x 8.5 cm (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Syria; Arabic Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Hats; Medals/Insignia
  - A portrait of a young boy wearing a swimsuit in the water., Circa 1955-1975; ref609; Photo Kermanik, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.9 x 9 cm (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Boys; Children; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Beaches; Water; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A group portrait of a man lifting up another man by his belt., Circa 1955-1975; ref610; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 14 x 8.8 cm (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Men; Outdoors; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a baby on a rocking horse., Circa 1955-1975; ref611; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.6 x 8.7 cm (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Toys; Children; Girls; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Syria
  - A postcard of Fouad I University (now Cairo University), Egypt., 1952; ref612; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 14 x 9 cm (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Postcards; English Writing; Egypt; Universities; Buildings; Architecture; Arabic Writing
  - A postcard of Beyrouth Avenue, Damascus., Circa 1950-1960; ref613; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 14.2 x 9.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Damascus, Syria; Mountains/Hills; Streets/Roads; Cars/Trucks; Postcards; Rivers; Mosques; Buildings; Transportation
  - A postcard of Damascus University (Caserne Hamidieh)., Circa 1950-1960; ref614; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.9 x 9 cm (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Universities; Damascus, Syria; Postcards; Buildings; Architecture; Military/Soldiers
  - Photo J. Ghazarian studio envelope., Circa 1950-1970; ref615; Photo J. Gazarian, Bab Touma, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.4 x 9.5 cm (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing; Signatures; Advertisements; Women; Art; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits
  - A group portrait of two women, three girls, and two boys indoors., Circa 1950-1970; ref616; Photo J. Gazarian, Bab Touma, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Women; Boys; Girls; Children; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Damascus, Syria
  - A portrait of a woman holding a dog (linked ref 616)., Circa 1950-1970; ref617; Photo J. Gazarian, Bab Touma, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Dogs; Animals; Women; Outdoors; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of three women, three girls, and two boys indoors (linked ref 616)., Circa 1950-1970; ref618; Photo J. Gazarian, Bab Touma, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Women; Children; Boys; Girls; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A portrait of a woman holding a dog (linked ref 617)., Circa 1950-1970; ref619; Photo J. Gazarian, Bab Touma, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Women; Dogs; Animals; Outdoors; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A portrait of a woman with a dog (linked ref 619)., Circa 1950-1970; ref620; Photo J. Gazarian, Bab Touma, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Women; Dogs; Outdoors; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Animals; Damascus, Syria
  - A portrait of a man in a suit outdoors., Circa 1955-1975; ref621; Studio Hovnan, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.3 x 5.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Men; Mountains/Hills; Outdoors; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A portrait of a man standing outdoors., Circa 1955-1975; ref622; Studio Hovnan, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.4 x 6.4 cm (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Men; Facial Hair; Mountains/Hills; Outdoors; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A group portrait of several women and one man sitting outdoors., Circa 1955-1975; ref623; Studio Hovnan, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.5 x 6.1 cm (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Men; Women; Damascus, Syria; Outdoors; Mountains/Hills; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A portrait of a man overlooking a balcony., Circa 1955-1975; ref624; Studio Hovnan, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.5 x 9.5 cm (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Men; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A studio envelope from Studio Hovnan., Circa 1955-1975; ref625; Studio Hovnan, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 13 x 9 cm (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing; Boys; Individual Portraits; Children; Dogs; Animals; Cameras
  - A studio envelope from Studio Omayad, Damascus., Circa 1955-1975; ref626; Studio Omayad, Rue Fardosse, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 11.8 x 8.1 cm (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing; Studio Photography
  - A group portrait of a man in a suit and three women outdoors., Circa 1955-1975; ref627; Studio Omayad, Rue Fardosse, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 5.9 x 8.6 cm (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Damascus, Syria; Men; Women; Outdoors; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of dressed up men and women in front of a statue of a woman., Circa 1955-1975; ref628; Studio Omayad, Rue Fardosse, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 8.9 x 6.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Damascus, Syria; Men; Women; Statues/Sculptures; Children; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A portrait of a woman sitting on a rock outdoors., Circa 1955-1975; ref629; Studio Omayad, Rue Fardosse, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 6.1 cm (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Photographic Prints; Outdoors; Women; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Damascus, Syria
  - A group portrait of three women indoors., Circa 1955-1975; ref630; Studio Omayad, Rue Fardosse, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 8.6 x 6.1 cm (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Damascus, Syria; Women; Furnishings; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of a woman and a man at a table., Circa 1955-1975; ref631; Studio Omayad, Rue Fardosse, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.2 x 7.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Damascus, Syria; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Drinks/Beverages
  - A group portrait of smiling man with his arm around a woman (linked ref 631)., Circa 1955-1975; ref632; Studio Omayad, Rue Fardosse, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.1 x 6.9 cm (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Men; Women; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Furnishings
  - A portrait of a woman posing indoors (linked ref632)., Circa 1955-1975; ref633; Studio Omayad, Rue Fardosse, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.1 x 7.1 cm (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Women; Jewelry; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Furnishings; Radios
  - An airport strip., Circa 1955-1975; ref634; Studio Omayad, Rue Fardosse, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Airplanes; Airports; Men; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Transportation
  - A group portrait of several people near a cliff., 1936; ref635; Studio Dunia, Derhagopian, Rue Fouad, 1er, Damas (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 8.6 x 5.7 cm (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Damascus, Syria; Men; Mountains/Hills; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Arabic Writing
  - A group portrait of nine men standing on a rock., Circa 1925-1945; ref636; Studio Dunia, Derhagopian, Rue Fouad, 1er, Damas (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 8.7 x 5.8 cm (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Men; Outdoors; Mountains/Hills; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Damascus, Syria
  - A group portrait of five men on a beach., Circa 1925-1945; ref637; Studio Dunia, Derhagopian, Rue Fouad, 1er, Damas (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 11.1 x 6.8 cm (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Men; Beaches; Water; Umbrellas/Parasols; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Coast; Facial Hair
  - A group portrait of seven women and two men in the woods., Circa 1925-1945; ref638; Studio Dunia, Derhagopian, Rue Fouad, 1er, Damas (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 6.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Women; Men; Forest/Woodlands; Outdoors; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Damascus, Syria; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of several people in the woods (linked ref 638)., Circa 1925-1945; ref639; Studio Dunia, Derhagopian, Rue Fouad, 1er, Damas (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 6.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Forest/Woodlands; Men; Women; Damascus, Syria; Outdoors; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of three men in a body of water., Circa 1925-1945; ref640; Studio Dunia, Derhagopian, Rue Fouad, 1er, Damas (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 11 x 6.7 cm (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Men; Water; Swimming; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Outdoors
  - A group portrait of four men on a beach., Circa 1925-1945; ref641; Studio Dunia, Derhagopian, Rue Fouad, 1er, Damas (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 11 x 6.7 cm (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Men; Beaches; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Water; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Damascus, Syria; Outdoors
  - A group portrait of several people standing on a cliff., 1936; ref642; Studio Dunia, Derhagopian, Rue Fouad, 1er, Damas (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 13.5 x 8.5 cm (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Mountains/Hills; Men; Postcards; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing; Outdoors
  - A group portrait of five men sitting in a tree., Circa 1925-1945; ref643; Studio Dunia, Derhagopian, Rue Fouad, 1er, Damas (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 14 x 8.8 cm (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Men; Forest/Woodlands; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Damascus, Syria
  - A group portrait of seven men wearing suits outdoors., 1936; ref644; Studio Dunia, Derhagopian, Rue Fouad, 1er, Damas (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 13.7 x 8.5 cm (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Men; Arabic Writing; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Outdoors; Damascus, Syria; Facial Hair
  - A group portrait of one man smoking with two other men indoors., Circa 1925-1945; ref645; Studio Dunia, Derhagopian, Rue Fouad, 1er, Damas (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 13.5 x 8.7 cm (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Men; Smoking; Cigarettes; Radios; Damascus, Syria; Furnishings; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair
  - A group portrait of many children and teenagers., Circa 1925-1945; ref646; Studio Dunia, Derhagopian, Rue Fouad, 1er, Damas (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 14 x 8.9 cm (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Boys; Children; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Damascus, Syria
  - A studio envelope from Studio Dunia, Derhagopian., Circa 1925-1945; ref647; Studio Dunia, Derhagopian, Rue Fouad, 1er, Damas (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 15.7 x 10.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing; Documents; Advertisements
  - A studio envelope from Studio Tuni and Safar, Damascus., Circa 1955-1975; ref648; Studio Tuni and Safar, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.8 x 8.9 cm (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing
  - A group portrait of a man holding a baby with a woman and child in the background., Circa 1955-1975; ref649; Studio Tuni and Safar, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Men; Women; Boys; Children; Outdoors; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
  - A group portrait of three men standing under an arch., Circa 1955-1975; ref650; Studio Tuni and Safar, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Men; Architecture; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Group Portraits
  - A portrait of a man standing next to a cow., Circa 1955-1975; ref651; Studio Tuni and Safar, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Men; Cattle/Cows; Animals; Forest/Woodlands; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Damascus, Syria; Outdoors
  - A group portrait of three men standing next to an animal (linked ref 651)., Circa 1955-1975; ref652; Studio Tuni and Safar, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Men; Cattle/Cows; Animals; Transportation; Cars/Trucks; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Outdoors
  - A group portrait of four men in an amphitheater., Circa 1955-1975; ref653; Studio Tuni and Safar, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Men; Architecture; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
  - A group portrait of five men posing indoors., Circa 1955-1975; ref654; Studio Tuni and Safar, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Men; Facial Hair; Furnishings; Clocks/Watches; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Damascus, Syria
  - A group portrait of four men, one of them wears a ghutrah., Circa 1955-1975; ref655; Studio Tuni and Safar, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Men; Regional/National Dress; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
  - A group portrait of eight men around a table, one of them wears a ghutrah., Circa 1955-1975; ref656; Studio Tuni and Safar, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Damascus, Syria; Food; Regional/National Dress; Men; Gatherings; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Facial Hair; Cameras
  - A group portrait of four men leaning on a car., Circa 1955-1975; ref657; Studio Tuni and Safar, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Men; Damascus, Syria; Cars/Trucks; Cigarettes; Smoking; Outdoors; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Transportation; Facial Hair; Streets/Roads